Contact

jabellau@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/juliebellau-mshcm-bsn-ccrn-k-neabc-55261763 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Inpatient

Healthcare Information Technology Hospitals

Certifications

NEA-BC

CCRN-K

Julie Bellau MSHCM, BSN, CCRN-K, NEA-BC

RN Director of Telemetry

Greater New Orleans Area

Summary

Experienced Director with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Healthcare Information Technology (HIT), Electronic Medical Record (EMR), Nursing, Clinical Research, and Inpatient Care. Strong professional with a Master of Science focused in Health/Health Care Administration/ Management from University of New Orleans.

Experience

Ochsner Health System
Director of Telemetry
October 2015 - Present (4 years 9 months)
Kenner

Ochsner Health System
4 years 7 months
ICU Clinical Coordinator
May 2013 - July 2015 (2 years 3 months)

RN Cardiovascular and Thoracic Surgery Clinic January 2011 - May 2013 (2 years 5 months)

North Oaks Health System
Critical Care RN
June 2002 - January 2011 (8 years 8 months)
Hammond La

Ochsner Health System
Staff Nurse
December 1991 - April 1996 (4 years 5 months)
New Orleans, Louisiana

Education

Louisiana State University
BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1988 - 1991)

University of New Orleans

Master of Science, Health/Health Care Administration/

Management · (2014 - 2016)